Be with me?
هل ستكون معي؟
Okay, my girlfriend.~
حسناً يا حبيبتي.
Okay.
تمام.
I realized I like you.
أدركت أنني معجب بك.
Can you like me back?
هل يمكنك أن تبادلني الإعجاب؟
What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل؟!
Mom!
أم!
Dad is gone.
رحل أبي.
Then...
ثم...
Then why didn’t you tell me?
فلماذا لم تخبرني؟
Didn't you tell me not to contact you?
ألم تطلب مني ألا أتصل بك؟
You don’t have to be afraid of anything now.
ليس عليك أن تخاف من أي شيء الآن.
From now on, I'll be by your side.
من الآن فصاعدًا، سأكون بجانبك.
Ice!
جليد!
Dad, is this him?
أبي، هل هذا هو؟
Yes.
نعم.
Why did you never tell me
لماذا لم تخبرني أبداً؟
that my brother was this handsome?
أن يكون أخي بهذا الوسامة؟
Are you leaving already?
هل ستغادرون بالفعل؟
I was going to invite you to stay for dinner.
كنت سأدعوك للبقاء لتناول العشاء.
I'm going to leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Thank you so much for inviting me.
شكراً جزيلاً على دعوتكم لي.
Happy birthday in advance.
عيد ميلاد سعيد مقدماً.
Take this to have on the way.
خذ هذا معك في الطريق.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
It's almost Ice's birthday.
اقترب عيد ميلاد آيس.
Happy birthday in advance!
عيد ميلاد سعيد مقدماً!
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Next time we're in Bangkok,
في المرة القادمة التي نزور فيها بانكوك،
let's have dinner.
لنتناول العشاء.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
But I have to go now.
لكن عليّ الذهاب الآن.
Well..
حسنًا..
Good bye.
مع السلامة.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
I'll take care of this.
سأتولى أمر هذا الأمر.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Good bye.
مع السلامة.
(I hope you enjoy it.)
(أتمنى أن تستمتعوا به.)
I invited you all here.
لقد دعوتكم جميعاً إلى هنا.
Because I want to talk to the director.
لأنني أريد التحدث إلى المدير.
I understand you're filming a short film.
أفهم أنك تقوم بتصوير فيلم قصير.
So is this a scene from the film or what.
هل هذا مشهد من الفيلم أم ماذا؟
It was during a break.
كان ذلك خلال فترة استراحة.
And did they have to hug.
وهل كان عليهما أن يتعانقا؟
Uncle.
عم.
That day Ice’s mom.
في ذلك اليوم، والدة آيس.
She arrived right when we were filming.
وصلت في اللحظة التي كنا نصور فيها.
And Ice had a small misunderstanding with his mom.
وحدث سوء فهم بسيط بين آيس ووالدته.
So Saint went to comfort him.
فذهب القديس ليواسيه.
That’s all.
هذا كل شيء.
Yes.
نعم.
As a director, if the actors aren’t comfortable.
بصفتي مخرجًا، إذا لم يكن الممثلون مرتاحين.
It’s hard to continue shooting.
من الصعب الاستمرار في التصوير.
But if outsiders see this.
لكن ماذا لو رأى الغرباء هذا؟
They’ll think differently.
سيفكرون بشكل مختلف.
I don’t think there’s anything strange here, uncle.
لا أعتقد أن هناك أي شيء غريب هنا يا عمي.
So does that mean you and Saint.
هل يعني ذلك أنت وسانت؟
Are actually dating?
هل هما يتواعدان فعلاً؟
Yes, we’ve been together for a long time.
نعم، لقد كنا معاً لفترة طويلة.
As friends.
كأصدقاء.
Friends?!
أصدقاء؟!
I’d never think of Saint as anything more.
لن أفكر في القديس أبدًا على أنه أكثر من ذلك.
Mr.Khom.
السيد خوم.
Mom.
أم.
What is this.
ما هذا.
I was investigating the short film they shot.
كنتُ أُجري تحقيقاً حول الفيلم القصير الذي قاموا بتصويره.
But now I’m suspicious about something else.
لكنني الآن أشك في شيء آخر.
So what exactly are Lanee and Saint?
إذن ما هما ليني وسانت تحديداً؟
Are they dating? Mrs.Jan?
هل هما يتواعدان؟ السيدة جان؟
I’ll speak with my daughter first.
سأتحدث مع ابنتي أولاً.
I’ll go too.
سأذهب أنا أيضاً.
What is going on, Lanee?
ما الذي يحدث يا ليني؟
I want to know everything.
أريد أن أعرف كل شيء.
Actually.
في الحقيقة.
I’m dating Sea.
أنا أواعد سي.
Why?
لماذا؟
You’ve never told me anything.
لم تخبرني بأي شيء قط.
I’m sorry mom.
أنا آسف يا أمي.
But I’ve been really uncomfortable.
لكنني كنت أشعر بعدم الارتياح حقاً.
And I think I need to tell you.
وأعتقد أنني بحاجة لإخبارك بذلك.
That I don’t like Saint.
أنا لا أحب القديس.
You can be angry at me.
يمكنك أن تغضب مني.
But I just don’t want to lie to myself anymore.
لكنني ببساطة لا أريد أن أكذب على نفسي بعد الآن.
I don’t want to lie to others.
لا أريد أن أكذب على الآخرين.
And I don’t want to lie to you anymore.
ولا أريد أن أكذب عليك بعد الآن.
Lanee.
ليني.
If you told me earlier.
لو أخبرتني بذلك سابقاً.
I wouldn’t have arranged your engagement with Saint.
ما كنت لأرتب خطوبتك مع سانت.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Since you said you’re dating Sea.
بما أنك قلت إنك تواعد سي.
I'm not stopping you.
لن أمنعك.
But
لكن
the problem now is,
المشكلة الآن هي،
I need to clear things up with Saint’s dad.
أحتاج إلى توضيح الأمور مع والد سانت.
I have one last question for you.
لدي سؤال أخير لك.
Yes.
نعم.
What are you and Saint?
ما أنت والقديس؟
We’re just actors working together.
نحن مجرد ممثلين نعمل معاً.
I think it’s normal.
أعتقد أن هذا طبيعي.
For actors to support each other.
لكي يدعم الممثلون بعضهم بعضاً.
Saint and I are professional.
أنا وسانت محترفان.
We don’t bring personal feelings into work.
لا ندخل مشاعرنا الشخصية في العمل.
If you have questions about the filming process.
إذا كانت لديك أسئلة حول عملية التصوير.
You can ask me.
يمكنك أن تسألني.
Mr.Khom.
السيد خوم.
We need to talk.
نحتاج إلى التحدث.
Yes, Mrs.Jan.
نعم، يا سيدتي جان.
Will you be okay.
هل ستكون بخير؟
If our kids don’t get engaged.
إذا لم يخطب أطفالنا.
Our kids must get married.
يجب أن يتزوج أبناؤنا.
My daughter is dating Sea.
ابنتي تواعد سي.
And I let her choose who she likes.
وتركتها تختار من تحب.
About making the kids post their online status
بخصوص جعل الأطفال ينشرون حالتهم على الإنترنت
as dating..
كما هو الحال في المواعدة..
I think we should remove it.
أعتقد أنه يجب علينا إزالته.
If we announce they’re not together.
إذا أعلنا أنهما ليسا معًا.
Investors will pull out.
سينسحب المستثمرون.
Mr. Khom.
السيد خوم.
You need to accept reality.
عليك أن تتقبل الواقع.
And I’m sure.
وأنا متأكد.
You already have a backup plan.
لديك بالفعل خطة احتياطية.
Right?
يمين؟
I think for now.
أعتقد ذلك في الوقت الحالي.
We shouldn’t do anything
لا ينبغي لنا أن نفعل أي شيء
that will alarm the investors.
هذا الأمر سيثير قلق المستثمرين.
I think.
أظن.
I need to reconsider you again.
أحتاج إلى إعادة النظر في أمرك مرة أخرى.
Sorry.
آسف.
For bringing you to meet my dad.
شكراً لك على تعريفك بوالدي.
It’s okay.
لا بأس.
How was my acting?
كيف كان أدائي التمثيلي؟
Did I really look stressed?
هل بدوت متوتراً حقاً؟
Saint and I work professionally.
أنا وسانت نعمل بشكل احترافي.
Don’t worry.
لا تقلق.
I’m fine.
أنا بخير.
Wait.
انتظر.
Saint.
القديس.
Is my Dad still making you follow me?
هل ما زال أبي يجبرك على اتباعي؟
I’m really sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
I don’t want to do this.
لا أريد أن أفعل هذا.
I’ve been following you guys on set.
لقد كنت أتابعكم في موقع التصوير.
Now I can’t keep up with class.
الآن لا أستطيع مواكبة الدروس.
If you don’t want to do it then
إذا كنت لا ترغب في القيام بذلك،
why do it.
لماذا نفعل ذلك؟
I have to.
على أن.
If I don’t.
إذا لم أفعل.
Your dad won’t keep me and my mom.
والدك لن يحتفظ بي وبأمي.
I don’t know if
لا أعرف إن كان
You two actually like each other or not.
هل أنتما معجبان ببعضكما حقاً أم لا؟
But I have my own life.
لكن لدي حياتي الخاصة.
If possible.
إذا كان ذلك ممكنا.
I want you two to
أريد منكما أن...
cause less drama and be less suspicious.
تسبب في دراما أقل وكن أقل إثارة للشك.
So I won’t have to follow you anymore.
لذلك لن أضطر إلى ملاحقتك بعد الآن.
Tonight you two should stay separately.
يجب أن تبقيا منفصلين الليلة.
Because your dad wants me and my mom to
لأن والدك يريدني أنا وأمي أن
monitor you both.
سنراقبكما أنتما الاثنين.
I’ll go then.
سأذهب إذن.
Woo!
وو!
And now we have
والآن لدينا
the last two awards.
الجائزتان الأخيرتان.
The two songs announced
تم الإعلان عن الأغنيتين
will be performed at the university countdown event
سيتم تقديم العرض في فعالية العد التنازلي بالجامعة
on New Year’s Eve.
في ليلة رأس السنة.
And without further delay.
وبدون مزيد من التأخير.
The first runner-up award.
جائزة المركز الثاني.
Goes to!!
يذهب إلى!!
Red Sunflower!
زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء!
to Red Sunflower!!!
إلى زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء!!!
By Karun Thongdee.
بقلم كارون ثونغدي.
Woohoo!! Yay!!
يا سلام!! ياااي!!
Yes.
نعم.
Great job everyone.
عمل رائع يا جماعة.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Yes.
نعم.
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
Ice let’s go.
هيا بنا يا آيس.
Woohoo!!
يا سلام!!
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
I told you we could do it.
قلت لك إننا نستطيع فعل ذلك.
I loved it, I loved it too.
أحببته، وأنا أيضاً أحببته.
Yes.
نعم.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Let’s invite the university president.
فلندعو رئيس الجامعة.
Mr.Nikom Saengarunawong to present the award
سيقوم السيد نيكوم سينجاروناوونغ بتقديم الجائزة
and take some photos.
والتقط بعض الصور.
Let it stay a secret love,
دعها تبقى سراً يا حبيبي،
like the lyrics say.
كما تقول كلمات الأغنية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let’s get a photo of the whole band.
لنلتقط صورة للفرقة بأكملها.
Is there something you dislike?
هل هناك شيء لا يعجبك؟
Since you gave it zero points.
بما أنك أعطيته صفرًا من النقاط.
Music is subjective, Mrs.Jan.
الموسيقى مسألة ذوق شخصي يا سيدتي جان.
Oh.
أوه.
I see.
أرى.
Seems like our preferences.
يبدو أن هذا يتوافق مع تفضيلاتنا.
Are very different.
مختلفان تماماً.
(Scores for Songwriting Competition 2025)
(نتائج مسابقة كتابة الأغاني 2025)
(Total: 0/100)
(المجموع: 0/100)
Woo!
وو!
Ice.
ثلج.
You’re incredible.
أنت رائع.
Second place.
المركز الثاني.
Mud, sit down. This my homie!
يا طين، اجلس. هذا صديقي!
I told you Ice has talent.
قلت لكم إن آيس موهوب.
Because you helped me record it.
لأنك ساعدتني في تسجيله.
You helped me so much.
لقد ساعدتني كثيراً.
So cool, bro.
رائع يا أخي.
Come on, let's celebrate.
هيا بنا نحتفل.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
One time!
مرة واحدة!
Yay!
ياي!
Ice,
جليد،
isn't Saint going to come?
ألن يأتي القديس؟
He's not coming.
لن يأتي.
Probably busy with stuff at home.
ربما يكون مشغولاً ببعض الأمور في المنزل.
Oh.
أوه.
And you, did you get
وأنت، هل حصلت على
an idea for the song performance yet?
هل لديك فكرة عن أداء الأغنية؟
I’ve thought of some ideas.
لقد فكرت في بعض الأفكار.
But nothing solid yet.
لكن لا شيء مؤكد حتى الآن.
Ice, you can schedule practice with me tomorrow.
يا آيس، يمكنك تحديد موعد للتدريب معي غداً.
Maybe while practicing,
ربما أثناء التدريب،
you’ll think of something.
ستفكر في شيء ما.
Music practice?
ممارسة الموسيقى؟
Yes!
نعم!
I’m free anyway.
أنا حر على أي حال.
Are you free?
هل أنت متفرّغة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
We’ll go.
سنذهب.
We won’t miss it.
لن نفتقده.
Really.
حقًا.
Let me come too.
دعني آتي أيضاً.
Hey, I’ll find a practice room for you guys.
حسنًا، سأجد لكم غرفة تدريب.
Don’t worry about me.
لا تقلق عليّ.
Then
ثم
tomorrow let’s practice music together.
غداً سنتدرب على الموسيقى معاً.
Let’s do it.
هيا بنا نفعلها.
Let’s do it!
هيا بنا نفعلها!
Woohoo!
يا سلام!
Music practice, bro!
ممارسة الموسيقى يا أخي!
Hey,
يا،
we still don’t have a club group photo.
ما زلنا لا نملك صورة جماعية للنادي.
Should we take a group picture.
هل نلتقط صورة جماعية؟
Yeah sure!
بالتأكيد!
That's a good idea.
هذه فكرة جيدة.
How do we take it?
كيف نتقبل الأمر؟
Well,
حسنًا،
who will take it.
من سيأخذها؟
Me?
أنا؟
Is that okay.
هل هذا مناسب؟
Okay.
تمام.
Here.
هنا.
Closer.
أقرب.
Okay.
تمام.
Everyone ready.
الجميع مستعدون.
Ready.
مستعد.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Today I got scolded by my dad again.
اليوم وبخني والدي مرة أخرى.
Just accept it.
تقبل الأمر فحسب.
Your dad won’t let you go easily.
لن يسمح لك والدك بالرحيل بسهولة.
Yeah.
نعم.
When will I get to be with Ice?
متى سأتمكن من أن أكون مع آيس؟
There will be a day.
سيأتي يوم.
When your dad accepts it.
عندما يتقبل والدك ذلك.
Oh.
أوه.
Oh, Saint.
يا قديس.
Don’t tell me you’re sleeping here again?
لا تقل لي أنك ستنام هنا مرة أخرى؟
Then where am I supposed to sleep?
إذن أين يُفترض بي أن أنام؟
You two sleep in that room.
تنامان أنتما الاثنان في تلك الغرفة.
I’ll sleep here.
سأنام هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Mud.
الطين.
Didn’t you say you wouldn’t get drunk.
ألم تقل إنك لن تسكر؟
Huh.
هاه.
I am drunk.
أنا ثمل.
Book, do you know.
هل تعلم عن الكتب؟
Ten didn’t walk me home.
لم يوصلني عشرة إلى المنزل.
Such a shitty person.
شخص حقير للغاية.
He ran off before it was even dark.
هرب قبل أن يحل الظلام.
But at least Ice came to drop me off.
لكن على الأقل جاء آيس ليُوصلني.
Otherwise I’d be wasted.
وإلا لكنت سأهدر كل شيء.
What?
ماذا؟
Go shower first.
اذهب للاستحمام أولاً.
Can I just sleep. You reek of alcohol.
هل يمكنني النوم فقط؟ رائحتك كريهة بسبب الكحول.
Go. I’ll just sleep.
اذهب. سأنام فقط.
Go shower.
اذهب للاستحمام.
I’ll shower tomorrow.
سأستحم غداً.
I'll take one tomorrow.
سآخذ واحدة غداً.
Then I’ll take you.
ثم سآخذك.
Will you go.
هل ستذهب؟
But you have to wash me.
لكن عليك أن تغسلني.
I’ll take you.
سآخذك.
How is it going to be?
كيف سيكون الوضع؟
Okay, okay.
حسناً، حسناً.
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
Fast.
سريع.
Go quickly.
انطلق بسرعة.
I’m going to shower with my boyfriend, Saint.
سأستحم مع صديقي، سانت.
See you, bro.
أراك لاحقاً يا أخي.
Go fast.
انطلق بسرعة.
It’s cold.
انها بارده.
Next time don’t drink so much.
في المرة القادمة لا تشرب كثيراً.
Then what should I do?
إذن ماذا عليّ أن أفعل؟
My heart loves it.
قلبي يعشق ذلك.
Are you addicted to alcohol?
هل أنت مدمن على الكحول؟
Not addicted to alcohol.
غير مدمن على الكحول.
I’m addicted to you.
أنا مدمن عليك.
Love you.
أحبك.
What are you saying.
ماذا تقول.
Wait.
انتظر.
Saint is here.
القديس هنا.
Good,
جيد،
makes it exciting.
يجعل الأمر مثيراً.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
It’s me.
هذا أنا.
Saint.
القديس.
I’m using Book’s phone to call.
أستخدم هاتف بوك لإجراء المكالمات.
Oh.
أوه.
I’m not coming back to the room tonight.
لن أعود إلى الغرفة الليلة.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Congrats
تهاني
on the award.
بشأن الجائزة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
You can come take pictures with the trophy too.
يمكنكم أيضاً التقاط الصور مع الكأس.
I brought it to the room already.
لقد أحضرته إلى الغرفة بالفعل.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Yeah.
نعم.
And the headphones
وسماعات الرأس
with your engraved name arrived yet?
هل وصل اسمك المحفور عليه بعد؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
It arrived faster than I expected.
وصل أسرع مما توقعت.
I like it.
أحبها.
It’s nothing.
لا شئ.
Ice.
ثلج.
I’m sorry.
أنا آسف.
For just standing there today.
لمجرد وقوفي هناك اليوم.
You handled everything alone.
لقد تعاملت مع كل شيء بمفردك.
This is already good enough.
هذا جيد بما فيه الكفاية.
Bear.
دُبٌّ.
I’m sorry.
أنا آسف.
That I used the song you helped write
لقد استخدمت الأغنية التي ساعدت في كتابتها
and didn’t credit you.
ولم ينسب الفضل إليك.
It’s okay.
لا بأس.
This song is my gift to you.
هذه الأغنية هي هديتي لك.
Yeah.
نعم.
Our lives right now are like the poet Li Bai.
حياتنا الآن تشبه حياة الشاعر لي باي.
How?
كيف؟
Are you going to jump into the river
هل ستقفز في النهر؟
and chase the moon?
ومطاردة القمر؟
If I could, I would.
لو استطعت لفعلت.
Then why didn’t you come?
فلماذا لم تأتِ إذن؟
Your dad’s henchman isn’t following you anymore,
لم يعد أحد أتباع والدك يتبعك،
right?
يمين؟
And where’s my phone
وأين هاتفي؟
Give it to Book.
أعطها للكتاب.
But anyway tomorrow.
على أي حال، غداً.
You have to come see me.
عليك أن تأتي لرؤيتي.
Yeah.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
I’ll hurry to you tomorrow.
سأسرع إليك غداً.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
When did you come back?
متى عدت؟
A while ago.
منذ فترة.
I saw your trophy.
لقد رأيت كأسك.
It's not only my trophy.
إنها ليست جائزتي فقط.
It’s your trophy too.
إنها جائزتك أيضاً.
Is this washed already?
هل تم غسل هذا بالفعل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
But
لكن
there are still the white clothes
لا تزال هناك الملابس البيضاء
that haven’t been washed yet.
التي لم يتم غسلها بعد.
Hey, do you have any?
هل لديك أي منها؟
Then we can wash them together with this pile.
ثم يمكننا غسلها مع هذه الكومة.
Yeah, I do.
نعم، أفعل.
A lot too.
كثيراً أيضاً.
Don’t forget your in-ears in your pocket again.
لا تنسَ سماعات الأذن في جيبك مرة أخرى.
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
If I forget them, the one who’ll be sad is you.
إذا نسيتهم، فأنت من سيحزن.
Yeah right.
أجل صحيح.
Come on,
تعال،
I’ll help hang them.
سأساعد في تعليقهم.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
this feels like that scene we filmed, right?
هذا يشبه المشهد الذي صورناه، أليس كذلك؟
The one where Seen and Kit were hanging clothes.
المشهد الذي كان فيه سين وكيت يعلقان الملابس.
Hey!
يا!
So that's how you're going to play?
إذن هكذا ستلعب؟
Come on.
تعال.
Doesn’t look like it at all.
لا يبدو الأمر كذلك على الإطلاق.
In that scene…
في ذلك المشهد...
they were about to kiss, right?
كانوا على وشك التقبيل، أليس كذلك؟
What kiss?
أي قبلة؟
I mean the scene where the mom interrupted them
أقصد المشهد الذي قاطعتهم فيه الأم
and found out that Seen and Kit liked each other?
واكتشفوا أن سين وكيت معجبان ببعضهما البعض؟
But
لكن
the mom isn’t here yet.
لم تصل الأم بعد.
Hello, Pas?
مرحباً، باس؟
Hello, Ice.
مرحباً يا آيس.
The music practice room is full,
غرفة التدريب الموسيقي ممتلئة،
so we’re thinking of practicing
لذلك نفكر في التدرب
at my home studio instead.
في الاستوديو المنزلي بدلاً من ذلك.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Can you send me the location
هل يمكنك إرسال الموقع إليّ؟
so I can go there?
هل يمكنني الذهاب إلى هناك؟
No need,
لا حاجة،
I’ll pick you up.
سآتي لأخذك.
Uh…
أوه…
Okay..
تمام..
Then I’ll send you my location.
ثم سأرسل لك موقعي.
You’re going to practice?
هل ستتدرب؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I’ll drive you.
سأوصلك بالسيارة.
Hey,
يا،
it’s fine.
لا بأس.
Pas is coming to pick me up.
سيأتي باس ليأخذني.
I’ll take you myself.
سأصطحبك بنفسي.
Hey.
يا.
Just drop me here.
أنزلني هنا فقط.
Today…
اليوم…
Can I go in and watch you practice?
هل يمكنني الدخول ومشاهدتك تتدرب؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Ice.
ثلج.
Hi, Pas.
مرحباً يا باس.
Am I late?
هل تأخرت؟
No, not at all.
لا، ليس على الإطلاق.
Ten and Mud just arrived too.
وصل كل من تين وماد للتو أيضاً.
How did Saint end up dropping you off?
كيف انتهى الأمر بسانت بإيصالك؟
Uh..
أوه..
Well, I was with Ice.
حسناً، كنت مع آيس.
Pas,
لا،
can I watch you and Ice practice today?
هل يمكنني مشاهدة تدريبك أنت وآيس اليوم؟
Ice, is that okay?
هل الثلج مناسب؟
Yeah, it’s fine.
نعم، لا بأس.
Just relax.
استرخي فقط.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
Your place is really cozy.
مكانك مريح للغاية.
Do you collect vintage stuff too?
هل تجمع الأشياء القديمة أيضاً؟
Oh.
أوه.
These are all my dad’s.
هذه كلها تخص والدي.
He likes vintage things.
إنه يحب الأشياء القديمة.
Pas!
لا!
This one is a rare model!
هذا نموذج نادر!
I remember there are only like 200 of these.
أتذكر أن هناك حوالي 200 منها فقط.
Yeah.
نعم.
My dad bought it for my mom
أبي اشتراه لأمي
when he proposed to her.
عندما تقدم لخطبتها.
And you, Ice? Is there a guitar you want?
وأنت يا آيس؟ هل هناك غيتار تريده؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
What model? Tell me,
أي طراز؟ أخبرني،
maybe I can find it for you.
ربما أستطيع أن أجده لك.
Well…
حسنًا…
actually…
في الحقيقة…
from this brand.
من هذه العلامة التجارية.
Oh. It looks pretty similar.
أوه. يبدو الأمر مشابهاً جداً.
(Thank you for coming into my life)
(شكراً لك على دخولك حياتي)
(as a ray of sunshine,)
(كشعاع من أشعة الشمس،)
(that gives meaning to a sunflower like me)
(هذا ما يعطي معنى لزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي)
(from once withered to bloom again.)
(من الذبول إلى الإزهار من جديد.)
(Thank you for making everyday)
(شكراً لك على جعل كل يوم مميزاً)
(no longer lonely as it once was.)
(لم تعد تشعر بالوحدة كما كانت من قبل.)
(I'll give back with all the love in my heart.)
(سأرد الجميل بكل الحب الذي في قلبي.)
(Always Red Sunflower of yours.)
(دائماً زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء خاصتك.)
Whoa.
يا إلهي!
This mic sounds insanely good.
صوت هذا الميكروفون رائع للغاية.
Of course it does.
بالطبع يفعل ذلك.
This is the Sennheiser MD 421.
هذا هو جهاز Sennheiser MD 421.
Almost twenty thousand baht each.
ما يقارب عشرين ألف باهت لكل منها.
You can use it for concerts and studio recording.
يمكنك استخدامه في الحفلات الموسيقية والتسجيلات الاستوديوية.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
I do.
أفعل.
Then I’ll give it to you.
سأعطيك إياه إذن.
Pas.
لا.
No, it’s okay.
لا، لا بأس.
I can’t accept it.
لا أستطيع قبول ذلك.
Just think of it as your birthday present.
اعتبرها هدية عيد ميلادك.
I really can’t, I’d feel too bad.
لا أستطيع حقاً، سأشعر بالسوء الشديد.
Keep it.
احتفظ به.
I really want you to use it.
أريدك حقاً أن تستخدمه.
Okay.
تمام.
Sure. Thank you so much.
بالتأكيد. شكراً جزيلاً لك.
So, how was what we practiced earlier?
إذن، كيف كان ما تدربنا عليه سابقاً؟
Was it okay?
هل كان ذلك جيداً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I think the instruments were a bit loud at the start.
أعتقد أن صوت الآلات الموسيقية كان مرتفعاً بعض الشيء في البداية.
Maybe if we bring Ice’s vocal up, it’d be clearer?
ربما لو رفعنا صوت آيس، لكان الأمر أوضح؟
Hey, Saint,
يا قديس،
you know music too?
هل تعرف الموسيقى أيضاً؟
No.
لا.
I just think listeners
أعتقد فقط أن المستمعين
would want to hear Ice’s voice clearly.
أود سماع صوت آيس بوضوح.
Hmm.
همم.
He’s right.
هو محق.
Then let’s give Ice a solo for the first verse.
فلنمنح آيس عزفاً منفرداً في المقطع الأول.
The rest of us will come in
أما البقية فسيدخلون
on verse 2 and 3.
في الآيتين الثانية والثالثة.
Ice, you can do a low baritone there.
يا آيس، يمكنك أن تؤدي دور الباريتون المنخفض هناك.
I’ll follow a bit behind.
سأتبعهم قليلاً.
Let’s make it verse 3 a dominant chord.
لنجعل المقطع الثالث عبارة عن وتر مهيمن.
It's a C#7.
إنها C#7.
Let’s switch to A, then C#7,
لننتقل إلى A، ثم C#7،
then F# minor, how’s that? Yeah.
ثم فا دييز الصغير، كيف يبدو؟ نعم.
Yeah, that works. Yes, perfect.
نعم، هذا مناسب. ممتاز.
Okay.
تمام.
Let’s run it again.
لنقم بتشغيله مرة أخرى.
Yep.
نعم.
Ice?
ثلج؟
Should we try flying a drone like this?
هل يجب أن نجرب تحليق طائرة بدون طيار كهذه؟
It looks cool.
يبدو رائعاً.
Aren’t you going overboard?
ألا تبالغ في الأمر؟
It’s just a university project.
إنه مجرد مشروع جامعي.
We’ll think about it later.
سنفكر في الأمر لاحقاً.
Let’s continue practice.
لنواصل التدريب.
Chord.
وتر.
Okay everyone, let’s keep going.
حسناً يا جماعة، لنكمل.
Okay.
تمام.
Alright, ready?
حسناً، هل أنت مستعد؟
Let’s try again.
لنحاول مرة أخرى.
If you’re stressed,
إذا كنت تشعر بالتوتر،
why not let the music carry you a bit?
لماذا لا تدع الموسيقى تأخذك في رحلة قصيرة؟
Do you always play music when you’re stressed?
هل تستمع دائمًا إلى الموسيقى عندما تكون متوترًا؟
Yep.
نعم.
I think everyone has a song
أعتقد أن لكل شخص أغنية
or melody they use to heal themselves.
أو لحن يستخدمونه للشفاء.
Do you have one?
هل لديك واحد؟
I used to.
كنت أفعل ذلك.
But now…
لكن الآن...
I feel like my song
أشعر وكأن أغنيتي
is becoming someone else’s song somehow.
أصبحت أغنية لشخص آخر بطريقة ما.
Oh?
أوه؟
Why do you think that?
لماذا تعتقد ذلك؟
Maybe someone else
ربما شخص آخر
can play that song better than me.
يستطيع عزف تلك الأغنية أفضل مني.
Hmm.
همم.
I think…
أظن…
everyone
الجميع
has different strengths.
لكل منها نقاط قوة مختلفة.
Like Robert Greene said in
كما قال روبرت غرين في
The Art of Seduction,
فن الإغواء،
he said that
قال ذلك
you don’t have to be good in the same way as others.
ليس عليك أن تكون جيداً بنفس طريقة الآخرين.
You just need to be good at being yourself.
كل ما عليك فعله هو أن تجيد أن تكون على طبيعتك.
If my dad
إذا كان والدي
understood even half of what you just said,
لم أفهم حتى نصف ما قلته للتو،
Um..
واحد..
I think I know now.
أعتقد أنني عرفت الآن.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
But I’ll excuse myself for now.
لكنني سأعتذر الآن.
Oh? Alright.
أوه؟ حسناً.
Okay.
تمام.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Good-bye.
مع السلامة.
Pas, thanks for bringing me home.
باس، شكراً لك على إيصالي إلى المنزل.
I had to come set up the mic anyway.
كان عليّ أن أحضر لأقوم بتركيب الميكروفون على أي حال.
But I just found out
لكنني اكتشفت ذلك للتو
you live in this apartment.
أنت تسكن في هذه الشقة.
Yeah, I rent here.
نعم، أنا أستأجر هنا.
Saint helps split the cost,
يساعد القديس في تقاسم التكاليف،
so it’s not expensive.
لذا فهو ليس مكلفاً.
Oh, so you live with Saint?
أوه، إذن أنت تعيش مع سانت؟
Yeah.
نعم.
How was practice today?
كيف كان التدريب اليوم؟
Good.
جيد.
I got to try some new things.
لقد سنحت لي فرصة تجربة بعض الأشياء الجديدة.
I’ll have to prepare a lot more for next time.
سأضطر إلى الاستعداد بشكل أفضل بكثير في المرة القادمة.
Yeah.
نعم.
But if I have more ideas,
لكن إذا كانت لديّ أفكار أخرى،
I’ll tell you right away.
سأخبرك على الفور.
I’m sure one day you’ll be an amazing artist.
أنا متأكد من أنك ستصبح فناناً مذهلاً يوماً ما.
Let me get your autograph now.
دعني أحصل على توقيعك الآن.
Right here.
هنا بالضبط.
That’ll be a long time from now.
سيستغرق ذلك وقتاً طويلاً من الآن.
For now, I’ll just practice with the mic you gave me.
في الوقت الحالي، سأكتفي بالتدرب باستخدام الميكروفون الذي أعطيتني إياه.
So that I'm used to it.
حتى أعتاد على ذلك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Give it a try.
جربها.
This is my room.
هذه غرفتي.
Wow,
رائع،
it’s pretty big.
إنه كبير جدًا.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
Happy birthday to you~
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Happy birthday, happy birthday~
عيد ميلاد سعيد، عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Woo!
وو!
Wishing you lots of happiness,
أتمنى لك الكثير من السعادة،
wealth, great health,
الثروة، والصحة الجيدة،
and may whoever you love love you back.
وأتمنى أن يحبك من تحب.
Happy birthday, Ice!
عيد ميلاد سعيد يا آيس!
Wishing you lots of happiness.
أتمنى لك الكثير من السعادة.
Make a wish!
تمنى أمنية!
Saint made this specially for you,
صنع القديس هذا خصيصاً لك،
super limited edition.
إصدار محدود للغاية.
This recipe, Ice used to love it as a kid.
كانت هذه الوصفة، آيس، تحبها كثيراً عندما كانت طفلة.
Here, go season the pork.
هيا، قم بتتبيل لحم الخنزير.
Hey.
يا.
Smells good, right?
رائحتها طيبة، أليس كذلك؟
Yay!
ياي!
Thank you so much, everyone.
شكراً جزيلاً لكم جميعاً.
Happy birthday, Ice!
عيد ميلاد سعيد يا آيس!
Have lots of happiness!
أتمنى لك الكثير من السعادة!
It’s okay, Ice.
لا بأس يا آيس.
I’ll come set up your mic again next time.
سأقوم بتركيب الميكروفون الخاص بك مرة أخرى في المرة القادمة.
Happy birthday.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Have fun celebrating with your friends.
استمتع بالاحتفال مع أصدقائك.
Pas,
لا،
stay and have cake with us first.
ابقَ معنا وتناول الكعكة أولاً.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Here,
هنا،
try it.
جربها.
See if it tastes good.
جرب طعمه لترى إن كان جيداً.
Sticky rice waterfall grilled pork cake.
كعكة لحم الخنزير المشوية مع الأرز اللزج.
How did you even come up with this?
كيف خطرت لك هذه الفكرة أصلاً؟
It tastes just like Mom’s.
طعمه تماماً مثل طعم طعام أمي.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
your mom helped me make it.
ساعدتني والدتك في صنعه.
Hi.
أهلاً.
Mom?
أم؟
Happy birthday, honey.
عيد ميلاد سعيد يا حبيبتي.
Mom…
أم…
I hope you’re the happiest you’ve ever been.
أتمنى أن تكون أسعد ما كنت عليه في حياتك.
Mom.
أم.
Here’s your birthday present.
إليك هدية عيد ميلادك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I rushed over so this is all I've got.
أسرعتُ إلى هناك، لذا هذا كل ما لدي.
The money you sent me.
المال الذي أرسلته لي.
I never spent it.
لم أنفقها أبداً.
I saved it all for you.
لقد ادخرت كل شيء من أجلك.
And I’ve been saving my own money too.
وكنت أدخر أموالي الخاصة أيضاً.
I thought…
ظننت...
if someday we got a chance to live together again,
إذا أتيحت لنا الفرصة يوماً ما للعيش معاً مرة أخرى،
you won’t have to struggle anymore.
لن تضطر إلى المعاناة بعد الآن.
I’m sorry that all this time
أنا آسف لأن كل هذا الوقت
I’ve been such a useless mother.
لقد كنت أماً عديمة الفائدة.
Don’t say that, Mom.
لا تقولي ذلك يا أمي.
I’ve been a coward.
لقد كنت جباناً.
I’ve been selfish.
لقد كنت أنانياً.
I always thought that
لطالما اعتقدت ذلك
if I could turn back time,
لو كان بإمكاني العودة بالزمن إلى الوراء،
I would storm in and take my child back,
كنت سأقتحم المكان وأستعيد طفلي،
no matter what happened.
بغض النظر عما حدث.
Live or die,
عش أو مت،
come what may.
مهما يكن.
And when you called me,
وعندما اتصلت بي،
I shouldn’t have pushed you away like that.
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أدفعك بعيداً هكذا.
It’s all in the past now, Mom.
كل شيء أصبح من الماضي الآن يا أمي.
Back then we were both just doing the best we could.
في ذلك الوقت، كنا نبذل قصارى جهدنا.
Your hand,
يدك،
what happened to it?
ماذا حدث له؟
Nothing, Mom.
لا شيء يا أمي.
Don’t worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن هذا
Ice,
جليد،
tell me the truth.
قل لي الحقيقة.
When I was running away from the debt collectors…
عندما كنت أهرب من محصلي الديون...
I fell while running
سقطت أثناء الجري
and something cut my hand.
وجرح شيء ما يدي.
Did it hurt a lot, sweetheart?
هل كان الأمر مؤلماً جداً يا حبيبتي؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
Everything just felt numb at that moment.
في تلك اللحظة، شعرتُ بالخدر التام.
I’m sorry.
أنا آسف.
I’m so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I’m really sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
It’s okay, Mom.
لا بأس يا أمي.
(Ice: Get home safely.)
(آيس: عد إلى المنزل بأمان.)
(Kaew: heart sticker)
(كايو: ملصق على شكل قلب)
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Your mom already left?
هل غادرت والدتك بالفعل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
She had to rush back to look after the homestay.
كان عليها أن تعود مسرعةً للاهتمام بالمنزل الذي تقيم فيه.
Look.
ينظر.
She even sent me a heart sticker.
بل إنها أرسلت لي ملصقاً على شكل قلب.
I’m sorry for not telling you first
أعتذر لعدم إخبارك أولاً
about inviting your mom.
بخصوص دعوة والدتك.
Thank you, Saint.
شكراً لك يا قديس.
It’s the best gift I’ve ever received in my life.
إنها أفضل هدية تلقيتها في حياتي.
Yeah.
نعم.
Seeing you happy
رؤيتك سعيداً
makes me happy too.
هذا يسعدني أيضاً.
Ice…
جليد…
I might not be good at guitar,
قد لا أكون بارعاً في العزف على الغيتار،
and
و
I might not understand music the way you do,
قد لا أفهم الموسيقى بالطريقة التي تفهمها بها،
but I want to stay by your side
لكنني أريد البقاء بجانبك
and keep supporting
واستمروا في تقديم الدعم
you like always.
كما هو الحال دائماً.
Like always.
كالعادة.
Actually, all this time
في الواقع، طوال هذا الوقت
I’ve been trying to help you.
لقد كنت أحاول مساعدتك.
Since the mafia forced you to pay off that debt,
بما أن المافيا أجبرتك على سداد ذلك الدين،
I was the one who called people to get them arrested.
كنت أنا من اتصل بالناس ليتم القبض عليهم.
I bought this apartment room for you.
اشتريت هذه الغرفة في الشقة خصيصاً لك.
I told Professor Sarah
أخبرتُ الأستاذة سارة
to let me look after you at the university,
لأدعك تعتني بك في الجامعة،
tried to find chances to see you,
حاولتُ إيجاد فرص لرؤيتك،
joined the short film project
انضم إلى مشروع الفيلم القصير
even though
بالرغم من
I can’t act at all.
لا أستطيع التمثيل إطلاقاً.
Why are you telling me all this?
لماذا تخبرني بكل هذا؟
From now on…
من الآن فصاعدًا...
let me be your boyfriend.
دعيني أكون حبيبك.
I promise
أعدك
I’ll make every one of your dreams come true.
سأحقق لك كل أحلامك.
Be my boyfriend, Ice.
كن حبيبي يا آيس.
No matter if my dad forbids it,
بغض النظر عما إذا كان والدي يمنع ذلك،
kicks me out,
يطردني،
or locks me up.
أو يحبسني.
I promise,
أعدك،
I swear, I’ll find my way to you.
أقسم أنني سأجد طريقي إليك.
I’ll protect you,
سأحميك،
no matter what happens.
بغض النظر عما يحدث.
I love you, Ice.
أحبك يا آيس.
(I once went through pain.)
(لقد مررت بالألم ذات مرة.)
(But then you came and gathered my broken heart.)
(لكنك أتيت بعد ذلك وجمعت قلبي المكسور.)
(You healed the wounds that never faded.)
(لقد شفيت الجروح التي لم تندمل أبدًا.)
(The feeling I have when I’m with you.)
(الشعور الذي ينتابني عندما أكون معك.)
(It changed the sky that was once dark)
(لقد غيّر ذلك السماء التي كانت مظلمة في السابق)
(into a light that made my heart beat strongly again.)
(إلى ضوء جعل قلبي ينبض بقوة مرة أخرى.)
(Thank you for coming into my life)
(شكراً لك على دخولك حياتي)
(as a ray of sunshine,)
(كشعاع من أشعة الشمس،)
(that gives meaning to a sunflower like me)
(هذا ما يعطي معنى لزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي)
(from once withered to bloom again.)
(من الذبول إلى الإزهار من جديد.)
(Thank you for making everyday)
(شكراً لك على جعل كل يوم مميزاً)
(no longer lonely as it once was.)
(لم تعد تشعر بالوحدة كما كانت من قبل.)
(I'll give back with all the love in my heart.)
(سأرد الجميل بكل الحب الذي في قلبي.)
(Always Red Sunflower of yours.)
(دائماً زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء خاصتك.)
Do you think Saint and Ice are together yet?
هل تعتقد أن سانت وآيس أصبحا معًا الآن؟
Maybe they’re secretly together…
ربما يكونان معًا سرًا...
like we were.
كما كنا.
I'm just scared that…
أنا خائف فقط من...
even though I already broke up with Saint,
على الرغم من أنني انفصلت بالفعل عن سانت،
Saint’s father still wouldn’t allow him
لكن والد سانت ما زال يرفض السماح له
to date Ice anyway.
على أي حال، سأواعد آيس.
People…
الناس…
if they really love each other,
إذا كانوا يحبون بعضهم البعض حقاً،
no matter how hard it is,
مهما كانت الصعوبة،
you can’t stop them.
لا يمكنك إيقافهم.
Believe me.
ثق بي.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Hey guys!
يا شباب!
Let’s toast!
فلنحتفل!
Come on, come on! Bottoms up!
هيا، هيا! فلنشرب حتى آخر قطرة!
Let’s go!
دعنا نذهب!
Can you show me first?
هل يمكنك أن تريني أولاً؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Show me how you do it.
أرني كيف تفعل ذلك.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I’ve had three glasses already,
لقد شربت ثلاثة أكواب بالفعل،
and I finished all of them.
وأنهيت جميعها.
But you guys haven’t finished any!
لكنكم لم تنتهوا من أي شيء!
Woah!
واو!
Book, drink more!
احجز، واشرب أكثر!
Getting there! Mud!
وصلنا إلى هناك! طين!
You’re drinking way too much.
أنت تشرب كثيراً.
Just a little bit!
قليلاً فقط!
Right, Pas?
صحيح، صحيح؟
Hey.
يا.
Right?
يمين؟
Who knows.
من يدري.
Do whatever you want.
افعل ما تشاء.
Huh?
هاه؟
Okay, that’s enough. Easy stuff.
حسناً، هذا يكفي. أمر سهل.
This is a friend from your faculty?
هل هذا صديق من كليتك؟
Ah.
آه.
This is my roommate.
هذا هو زميلي في السكن.
Book.
كتاب.
Yep.
نعم.
Oh.
أوه.
Ah, nice to meet you, Book.
أهلا بك يا كتاب.
Same here.
نفس الشيء هنا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I..
أنا..
I’m gonna go to the bathroom for a bit.
سأذهب إلى الحمام قليلاً.
Oh, sure.
أوه، بالتأكيد.
(Even if…)
(حتى لو…)
(Even if we can’t be lovers…)
(حتى لو لم نتمكن من أن نكون حبيبين...)
(I’ll still be your fan, Ice. From Pas.)
(سأظل معجبًا بك يا آيس. من باس.)
Thank you for coming into my life
شكراً لك على دخولك حياتي
as a ray of sunshine,
كشعاع من أشعة الشمس،
that gives meaning to a sunflower like me
هذا ما يعطي معنى لزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي
from once withered to bloom again.
من الذبول إلى الإزهار من جديد.
Thank you for making everyday
شكراً لك على جعل كل يوم مميزاً
no longer lonely as it once was.
لم يعد المكان يشعر بالوحدة كما كان في السابق.
I'll give back with all the love in my heart.
سأرد الجميل بكل الحب الذي في قلبي.
Always Red Sunflower of yours.
زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء خاصتك دائماً.
Hey!
يا!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
That tickles.
هذا يُدغدغ.
Day by day you’re getting clingier,
يوماً بعد يوم تزداد تعلقاً بي،
just like a little bear.
تمامًا مثل دب صغير.
Please,
لو سمحت،
you’re the one who’s clingy,
أنت الشخص المتشبث،
you little panda cub.
يا صغير الباندا.
Ice…
جليد…
I love you.
أحبك.
I liked you ever since
لقد أحببتك منذ ذلك الحين
the first moment you stood in front of my house.
اللحظة الأولى التي وقفت فيها أمام منزلي.
I liked you too
لقد أعجبت بك أيضاً
ever since you gave me your shoes at the bus stop.
منذ أن أعطيتني حذائك في موقف الحافلات.
I love you, Saint.
أحبك يا قديس.
Goodnight.
طاب مساؤك.
(Thank you for coming into my life)
(شكراً لك على دخولك حياتي)
(as a ray of sunshine,)
(كشعاع من أشعة الشمس،)
(that gives meaning to a sunflower like me)
(هذا ما يعطي معنى لزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي)
(from once withered to bloom again.)
(من الذبول إلى الإزهار من جديد.)
(Thank you for making everyday)
(شكراً لك على جعل كل يوم مميزاً)
(no longer lonely as it once was.)
(لم تعد تشعر بالوحدة كما كانت من قبل.)
(I'll give back with all the love in my heart.)
(سأرد الجميل بكل الحب الذي في قلبي.)
(Always Red Sunflower of yours.)
(دائماً زهرة عباد الشمس الحمراء خاصتك.)
(The distance from the sun to a sunflower like me.)
(المسافة بين الشمس وزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي.)
(No matter how far, the light will always reach me.)
(مهما كانت المسافة، سيصلني النور دائمًا.)
(And nobody can ever take your place)
(ولا يمكن لأحد أن يحل محلك أبداً)
(because love has tied our hearts together.)
(لأن الحب قد ربط قلوبنا معًا.)
(I promise that every second, there is only you.)
(أعدك أنه في كل ثانية، أنت وحدك.)
(Thank you for coming into my life)
(شكراً لك على دخولك حياتي)
(as a ray of sunshine,)
(كشعاع من أشعة الشمس،)
(that gives meaning to a sunflower like me)
(هذا ما يعطي معنى لزهرة عباد الشمس مثلي)
(from once withered to bloom again.)
(من الذبول إلى الإزهار من جديد.)
(Thank you for making everyday)
(شكراً لك على جعل كل يوم مميزاً)
Now that you're my boyfriend.
الآن وقد أصبحت حبيبي.
Is there anything else you want to do?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر ترغب في القيام به؟
You can do anything you want now.
يمكنك فعل أي شيء تريده الآن.
I'm going to hug you
سأعانقك
and tell you sweet dreams every night.
وأتمنى لك أحلاماً سعيدة كل ليلة.
When you understand what I'm trying to say?!
متى ستفهم ما أحاول قوله؟!
I...
أنا...
You never consider my feelings!
أنت لا تراعي مشاعري أبداً!
Do you know that?
هل تعلم ذلك؟
I think we should spend some time apart
أعتقد أننا يجب أن نقضي بعض الوقت منفصلين
to think our relationship over.
لنفكر في علاقتنا.
Ten, can I sleep over?
عشرة، هل يمكنني المبيت؟
If one day I don't let you hug me.
إذا لم أسمح لك يوماً ما باحتضاني.
What would you do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
I've never thought of that day.
لم أفكر في ذلك اليوم قط.
You don't want to hold my hand
لا تريد أن تمسك بيدي
because you're embarrassed of me around other people?
لأنك تشعر بالحرج مني أمام الآخرين؟
Forget about other people.
انسَ أمر الآخرين.
I only care about my boyfriend.
أنا لا أهتم إلا بصديقي.
Alex from freshman year.
أليكس من السنة الأولى.
He has no record of attending any classes,
ليس لديه أي سجل لحضور أي دروس،
except for Professor Mint's.
باستثناء البروفيسور مينت.
For us to defeat
لكي نهزم
someone as cautious as him,
شخص حذر مثله،
we must expose him
يجب أن نكشف أمره
without giving him a chance to redeem himself.
دون منحه فرصة لتصحيح أخطائه.